plr.me 2016-06-25

# Privacy Policy

PLR.me values the trust our customers place on us. This privacy statement is intended to explain what PLR.me does with your information, and what you can expect from us. If you have additional questions or would like further information on this topic, please contact us. PLR.me may update this policy from time to time. Please check the policy periodically for changes.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

**Types and Uses of Personal Information**

Your personal information is used in the following ways:  
**  
****User IDs and Passwords** : Provide you with access to the members areas and to protected content.

**IP Address** : An IP address is recorded at the time of order placement. This is used only for the purposes of fraud prevention.

**Account Information** : Tells us more about who you are, how to contact you, and your billing information. Also contains any preferences you have provided, such as e-mail format and interests.

**Customer Feedback and Support** : Provides a mechanism for requesting information from PLR.me. Also used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and site design.

**E-mail Correspondence** : Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information, email newsletters about PLR.me, our products, and services.

**Transactions** : Show which products and services you have requested.

We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage.

**Security Measures**

We protect the personal information you share with us. For example, if you make an online purchase with us, we encrypt your credit card number. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job.

Authorized third-party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We only provide third-party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third-parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

We may collect and possibly share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of PLR.me’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Data Retention**

PLR.me will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

**Linked Web Sites**

We provide links to third-party sites. Since we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites. PLR.me is not responsible for third party content.

**Cookies**

The PLR.me website may occasionally use cookies. Cookies help us provide a better user experience by measuring which web pages are of greatest interest. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access the members only area of the website.

Current versions of web browsers offer enhanced user controls regarding the placement and duration of both first and third party cookies. Search for "cookies" under your Web browser’s help menu for more information on cookie management features available to you.

**Analytics Tools, Remarketing and Advertising**

We use analytics tools and other third party technologies, such as Google Analytics and Facebook, to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our online Sites and/or Services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.

The third party analytics companies who collect information on our Sites and/or Services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

In addition to our use of technologies as described herein, we may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your use of ACQYR Inc Sites and/or Services and to otherwise collect and use data about your use of ACQYR Inc Sites and/or Services. For more information about this practice, please see the "Third Party Advertising Technologies" section below.

We also use third party remarketing to advertise across the Internet. Remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the PLR.me website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER. The cookie is used to say “This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page.” This allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.”

You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads) or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746), and [Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363).

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

      **•** On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

      **•** By emailing us

      **•** By calling us

      **•** By logging in to their account

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email

      **•** Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN-SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

      **•** Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

      **•** Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

      **•** We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.

      **•** Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

      **•** NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

      **•** Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

      **•** Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

      **•** Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

      **•** Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

      **•** Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

**Your Consent To This Agreement**

By using the PLR.me site, you consent to the collection and use of information by PLR.me as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Whom do I contact if I have additional questions or concerns about this policy?**

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact us.

Note: This policy may be modified from time to time. You are encouraged to review this policy each time you visit this site.

_Dated: February  8, 2015_
